If you’re a React developer, there’s no
doubt you’ve heard about React 18.
如果你是 React 开发人员，那么毫无疑问你已听说过 React 18 了。
Now, while there is still a lot more to come,
I thought you might want to see what are its
现在，尽管你有工作要忙，但我想你可能想了解下它到底有哪些
top new features.
主要的新特性。
The first one is automatic batching.
第一个是自动批处理。
Long story short, batching in React is whenever
multiple state updates are combined into a
长话短说，React 中的批处理是将多个状态更新组合成一个
single re-render.
单次重新渲染。
In this example, the component would only
be rendered once after handleClick is called,
在这个例子中，组件只会在 handleClick 被调用后渲染一次，
although we might think setCount and setClicked
would trigger two re-renders.
尽管我们可能认为 setCount 和 setClicked 会触发两次重新渲染。
Now, while this works well at the moment,
if you’re calling multiple state updates
现在，虽然目前这很有效，但如果你正在调用多个状态更新
in a different context such as a promise,
a callback, or a timeout, React won’t batch
在不同的上下文中，例如承诺、回调或超时，React 不会批处理
these two updates into one and you’ll get
two re-renders when only one would have been
将这两个更新合二为一，当只有一个时，你将获得两次重新渲染
needed.
需要。
With React 18, all these use-cases will now
be covered and state updates will be batched
使用 React 18，现在将涵盖所有这些用例，并且将批量更新状态
automatically no matter what’s the context.
无论上下文如何，都会自动执行。
This might remind you of unstable_batchedUpdates
that was doing exactly this, well now, React
这可能会让你想起正在做这个的unstable_batchedUpdates，好吧，React
will do it for you by default.
默认情况下会为你做。
Also, if you happen not to want these updates
to be batched, you’ll need to use flushSync
此外，如果你不希望批量更新这些更新，则需要使用 flushSync
that will re-render your component every time
it’s done running the function you’re
每次完成运行你正在运行的功能时，它将重新渲染你的组件
passing it to.
传递给。
So with the following, your component would
render twice instead of just one time.
因此，使用以下内容，你的组件将渲染两次而不是一次。
Moving on to transitions, a really big new
feature, which allows you “to tell React
继续过渡，这是一个非常重要的新功能，它允许你“告诉 React
which updates are urgent, and which are not”.
哪些更新是紧急的，哪些不是”。
A good example of that is a search input that
should filter out a list of elements.
一个很好的例子是应该过滤掉元素列表的搜索输入。
So if you’re updating a search input, you’d
want its value to change as we type, although
因此，如果你要更新搜索输入，你会希望它的值随着我们的输入而改变，尽管
the search results might appear in a second
phase when we’re done typing.
当我们完成输入时，搜索结果可能会出现在第二阶段。
This is where we could mark the input value
change as an urgent update, and the elements
这是我们可以将输入值更改标记为紧急更新的地方，并且元素
filtering as secondary also called now a transition.
作为次要过滤现在也称为过渡。
Transitions can be interrupted by urgent updates
and previous transitions that are no longer
过渡可能会被紧急更新和不再存在的先前过渡中断
relevant will be dismissed.
相关的将被解雇。
This allows the user interface to only show
its most up-to-date state and skip secondary
这允许用户界面仅显示其最新状态并跳过次要状态
updates, transitions, that might be slower
to compute and sometimes return intermediate
更新、转换，计算速度可能较慢，有时返回中间值
states that are irrelevant.
不相关的状态。
As you can see here, we’re marking the input
value change as urgent, and run our secondary
正如你在此处看到的，我们将输入值更改标记为紧急，并运行我们的辅助
update inside a transition as it might trigger
slow computations and could freeze or slow
在转换内更新，因为它可能会触发缓慢的计算并且可能会冻结或减慢
down the whole user experience as we type.
在我们键入时降低整个用户体验。
startTransition is great for any update “you
want to move to the background” such as
startTransition 非常适合“你想移到后台”的任何更新，例如
slow and complex rendering tasks or when
updates rely on fetching data that might take
缓慢而复杂的渲染任务，或者当更新依赖于获取可能需要的数据时
time due to a slow network.
由于网速慢。
If you have a React application, you might
know that if you’re not using Server-Side
如果你有一个 React 应用程序，你可能知道如果你不使用服务器端
Rendering aka SSR, your website always appears
blank when you run it for the first time.
渲染又名 SSR，你的网站在你第一次运行时总是显示为空白。
That is because the browser needs to fetch
and read your JavaScript which takes some
那是因为浏览器需要获取和读取你的 JavaScript，这需要一些时间
time before your components load and the page
becomes interactive.
在你的组件加载和页面变得可交互之前的时间。
With SSR however, the user sees how your app
looks directly but without all the interactions
然而，使用 SSR，用户可以直接看到你的应用程序的外观，但没有所有交互
while the JavaScript is being loaded.
在加载 JavaScript 时。
The way it works is by rendering all the
components on the server first, then sending
它的工作方式是先渲染服务器上的所有组件，然后发送
the result as HTML to the browser.
结果作为 HTML 发送到浏览器。
After that, the JavaScript is loaded as usual
and the HTML magically becomes interactive
之后，JavaScript 像往常一样加载，HTML 神奇地变成了交互式
by what is called hydration.
通过所谓的水合作用。
This turns your static HTML elements into
your dynamic React components as you know
如你所知，这会将你的静态 HTML 元素转换为动态 React 组件
them.
他们。
The main problem with this approach is that
as long as the JavaScript hasn’t been fetched,
这种方法的主要问题是，只要没有获取 JavaScript，
loaded, and your HTML hydrated, your page
won’t be interactive.
加载，并且你的 HTML 已水合，你的页面将无法交互。
To solve this waterfall issue, React 18 now
offers two new features for SSR:
为了解决这个瀑布问题，React 18 现在为 SSR 提供​​了两个新功能：
Streaming HTML and Selective Hydration.
流式 HTML 和选择性水合作用。
Put simply, streaming HTML means that the
server can send pieces of your components
简而言之，流式 HTML 意味着服务器可以发送你的组件片段
as they get rendered.
当它们被渲染时。
This works by using Suspense, where you’d
say which parts of your application will take
这通过使用 Suspense 起作用，你可以在其中说明应用程序的哪些部分
longer to load and which ones
should be rendered directly.
加载时间更长，哪些应该直接渲染。
If you think of an article with comments where
the article is the critical part of the page,
如果你想到一篇带有评论的文章，​​其中该文章是页面的关键部分，
you could say load the article but don’t
wait for the comments to be ready to send
你可以说加载文章，但不要等待评论准备好发送
HTML to the browser.
HTML 到浏览器。
You could show a spinner instead using
Suspense and once the comments are ready,
你可以使用 Suspense 显示一个微调器，一旦评论准备好，
React will send new bits of HTML that will
replace the spinner in place.
React 将发送新的 HTML 位来替换原位的微调器。
Now, the second new feature, selective hydration,
is quite a game-changer.
现在，第二个新功能，选择性补水，完全改变了游戏规则。
Where before you’d have to wait for every
component to be rendered to begin hydration,
在你必须等待每个组件被渲染开始水化之前，
leading to code splitting problems, components
now wrapped with Suspense
导致代码拆分问题，组件现在用 Suspense 包裹
won’t block hydration anymore.
不会再阻碍水合作用了。
In other words, if we go back to our article
page, the comments that we wrapped with
换句话说，如果我们回到我们的文章页面，我们包裹的评论
Suspense won’t block the article and other
components to be hydrated.
悬念不会阻止文章和其他组件被水化。
Every ready component will start hydrating
and the comments will too, once the browser
一旦浏览器打开，每个准备好的组件都会开始补水，评论也会
gets both its content and JavaScript code.
获取其内容和 JavaScript 代码。
The last crazy thing about selective hydration
is that if you happen to interact with one
关于选择性补水的最后一件疯狂的事情是，如果你碰巧与一个人互动
of the components before it’s been fully
hydrated, meaning you click somewhere, for
完全水合之前的组件，这意味着你单击某处，对于
example, React will prioritise this
component’s hydration.
例如，React 会优先考虑这个组件的水合作用。
This ensures that the most critical interactions
are to be repeated as soon as we can hydrate
这确保了最关键的相互作用在我们可以水合后立即重复
the related component, making sure it’s
hydrated before the others.
相关成分，确保它在其他成分之前被水合。
All right, that’s all for today.
好了，今天就到这里。
You can find great explanations of all these
new features on the official repository which
你可以在官方存储库中找到所有这些新功能的详细解释
is linked in the description.
已在说明中链接。
Remember to subscribe if you don’t want
to miss more videos like this one.
如果你不想错过更多这样的视频，请记得订阅。
Thanks for watching and see you next time :)
感谢收看，我们下期再见：）